[{"answer": "I'm happy you like it", "docId": "It_s-Complicated.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " Hello", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " -- I'm having an out of body experience", "docId": "It_s-Complicated.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Please shut up.    I'm so dizzy", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " WHAT is wrong with us", "docId": "It_s-Complicated.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "A great time? This is the dumbest thing two people have ever done.  my friend sits on the edge of the tub.    This is news to him", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "-- my friend, I take my hat off to you", "docId": "It_s-Complicated.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Not totally out of nowhere, my friend...if you know what I mean", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I know. Okay, I've got to hit the road, guys.  32. JANE  Thanks for staying. So proud of you. Be good. Call me if you need me.", "docId": "It_s-Complicated.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " It was", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " It's been a process", "docId": "It_s-Complicated.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "In two more years I'll begin to feel normal? Why am I having trouble seeing that as good news", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "my friend, come on. This is just too weird. We have to just never do what we did", "docId": "It_s-Complicated.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " No! It wasn't! On no levels was it right", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "What? When did this happen? Where'd you meet him", "docId": "It_s-Complicated.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "In that place??? Last week", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Going to the bathroom", "docId": "It_s-Complicated.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Yes it did", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "-- Well that's nice to hear after all these years...  Did you forget to take any of your medications today", "docId": "It_s-Complicated.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What all did you take? JAKE Uh....Lipitor, baby aspirin..  Flomax", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I mean do you smoke pot?! I haven't asked anyone that question since I was twent", "docId": "It_s-Complicated.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Oh my God, we have kids the same age! And I haven't had any since my kids were born either!!! Except for tonight. I had one hit off of this", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "But I was thinking it", "docId": "It_s-Complicated.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "How can you be too old for me when I'm older than you", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Knowing how to be divorced is next to impossible... and sometimes over the years, I've thought that your Dad and I weren't quite finished. And, as it turns out, we weren't. So I went out of my comfort zone, which, I found out, if you're really honest with yourself, isn't all that comforting. So, I experimented with a part of myself. I wanted to find out if, after all these years there was still something there between us", "docId": "It_s-Complicated.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "There kinda was", "qsentId": 26}]